Catholic Charities USA
The American Catholic Research Center and University Archives
- Series 9: Publications, 1910-2015; (35 Boxes)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings, 1982 (Box 265, Folder 10)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings, 1983 (Box 265, Folder 11)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings (1), 1984 (Box 265, Folder 12)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings (2), 1984 (Box 265, Folder 13)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings, 1985-1987 (Box 265, Folder 14)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 265, Folder 15)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 265, Folder 16)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Membership, 1975-1992 (Box 265, Folder 17)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Board Publication Committee Meeting, 1982 (Box 265, Folder 18)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Article and Book Review Information (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Boystown Research, 1975 (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: College of St. Teresa, 1985 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1978-1982 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with other Journals, 1983-1986 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Editorial Planning and Ideas, 1978-1980 (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Lecture, 1989-1990 (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Letters to the Editor and Personal, 1976-1986 (Box 266, Folder 9)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: National Family Planning Project, 1978-1980 (Box 266, Folder 10)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Off Prints, 1980-1982 (Box 266, Folder 11)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Papal Issue, 1986 (Box 266, Folder 12)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Proposals, 1984 (Box 266, Folder 13)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Publishers, 1980-1983 (Box 266, Folder 14)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Religion and Social Work, 1980-1986 (Box 266, Folder 15)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Requests, 1975-1983 (Box 266, Folder 16)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Samples and Individuals Copies, 1975-1980 (Box 266, Folder 17)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Sandoval Paper, 1977-1978 (Box 266, Folder 18)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Social Thought, 1975-1984 (Box 266, Folder 19)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Study of Social Work Journals, 1977-1979 (Box 266, Folder 20)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Subscription Numbers, ca. 1986 (Box 266, Folder 21)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Articles Submited, 1975-1976 (Box 266, Folder 22)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Blacks, 1976 (Box 266, Folder 23)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Authors, 1976-1977 (Box 266, Folder 24)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Authors, 1978 (Box 266, Folder 25)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Authors, 1983 (Box 266, Folder 26)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Authors, 1984 (Box 266, Folder 27)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Authors, 1985 (Box 266, Folder 28)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Authors, 1986 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Authors, 1987 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Authors, 1988 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Referees, 1982-1984 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Referees, 1984-1985 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Correspondence with Referees, 1986-1988 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Reports with Referees, 1983, 1985 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Reports with Referees, 1987-1988 (Box 267, Folder 8)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Accepted Papers, 1987, 1989 (Box 267, Folder 9)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Accepted Papers, 1990 (Box 267, Folder 10)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Accepted Papers, 1991 (Box 267, Folder 11)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers, 1976-1980 (Box 267, Folder 12)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers, 1986 (Box 267, Folder 13)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers, 1987 (Box 267, Folder 14)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers (1), 1988 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers (2), 1988 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers (1), 1989 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers (2), 1989 (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers (2), 1990 (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Rejected Papers (2), 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Miscellaneous Papers (1), 1982-1984 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Miscellaneous Papers (2), 1982-1984 (Box 268, Folder 8)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Miscellaneous Papers (3), 1982-1984 (Box 268, Folder 9)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Eleanor Judah - General (1), 1989-1992 (Box 268, Folder 10)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Eleanor Judah - General (2), 1989-1992 (Box 268, Folder 11)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Eleanor Judah - Lecture, 1989-1990 (Box 268, Folder 12)
  - Social Thought Editorial Files: Eleanor Judah - Ending Memo to Board/Transition, 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 13)
  - Social Thought: Volumes 1-2, 1975-1976 (Box 269)
    Bound Volume (Blue)
  - Social Thought: Volumes 3-4, 1977-1978 (Box 269)
    Bound Volume (Red)
  - Social Thought: Volume 5, 1979 (Box 269)
  - Social Thought: Volumes 6-7, 1980-1981 (Box 269)
  - Social Thought: Volumes 8-9, 1982-1983 (Box 269)
  - Social Thought: Volumes 9-10, 1983-1984 (Box 269)
  - Social Thought: Volumes 11-12, 1985-1986 (Box 269)
  - Social Thought: Volumes 13-14, 1987-1988 (Box 269)
  - Social Thought: Volumes 15-16, 1989-1990 (Box 269)
  - Social Thought: Volume 17, 1991 (Box 269)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1976 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1977 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1978 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1979 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1980 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1981 (Box 270, Folder 6)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1982 (Box 270, Folder 7)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1983 (Box 270, Folder 8)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1984 (Box 270, Folder 9)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (1), 1985 (Box 270, Folder 10)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (2), 1985 (Box 270, Folder 11)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1986 (Box 270, Folder 12)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues, 1987 (Box 270, Folder 13)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issue - Special Issue Pope John Paul II, 1987 (Box 270, Folder 14)
    Hardback
  - Social Thought: Loose Issue - Special Issue Pope John Paul II, 1987 (Box 270, Folder 15)
    Paperback
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (1), 1988 (Box 270, Folder 16)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (2), 1988 (Box 270, Folder 17)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (1), 1989 (Box 270, Folder 18)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (2), 1989 (Box 270, Folder 19)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (1), 1990 (Box 270, Folder 20)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (2), 1990 (Box 270, Folder 21)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (1), 1991 (Box 270, Folder 22)
  - Social Thought: Loose Issues (2), 1991 (Box 270, Folder 23)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 1-3, 1974-1976 (Box 271)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 4-5, 1977-1978 (Box 271)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 7-8, 1980-1981 (Box 271)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 9-10, 1982-1983 (Box 271)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 11-12, 1984-1985 (Box 271)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 13-14, 1986-1987 (Box 271)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 15-17, 1988-1990 (Box 271)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 18-19, 1991-1992 (Box 272)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 20-22, 1993-1995 (Box 272)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 23-24 (1), 1996-1997 (Box 272)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 23-24 (2), 1996-1997 (Box 272)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 25-28, 1998-2001 (Box 272)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 29-30, 2002-2003 (Box 272)
  - Catholic Charities USA: Bound, Volumes 31-33, 2004-2006 (Box 272)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1974 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1975 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1976 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1977 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1978 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1979 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1980 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1981 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1982 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Charities USA (1), 1983 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Charities USA (2), 1983 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Charities USA (1), 1984 (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Charities USA (2), 1984 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Charities USA (1), 1985 (Box 273, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Charities USA (2), 1985 (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1986 (Box 273, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1987 (Box 273, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1988 (Box 273, Folder 12)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1989 (Box 273, Folder 13)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1990 (Box 273, Folder 14)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1991 (Box 273, Folder 15)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1992 (Box 273, Folder 16)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1993 (Box 273, Folder 17)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1994 (Box 273, Folder 18)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1995 (Box 273, Folder 19)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1996 (Box 273, Folder 20)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1997 (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1998 (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 1999 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 2008 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 2009 (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 2010 (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 2011 (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 2012 (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 2013 (Box 274, Folder 9)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 2014 (Box 274, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Charities USA, 2015 (Box 274, Folder 11)
  - Executive Notes, 1998-2002 (Box 274, Folder 12)
  - Executive Notes, 2003-2006 (Box 274, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1974 (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Annual Survey, 1975 (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Annual Survey, 1976 (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Annual Survey, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Annual Survey, 1978 (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Annual Survey, 1979 (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Annual Survey, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - Annual Survey, 1981 (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - Annual Survey, 1982 (Box 275, Folder 9)
  - Annual Survey, 1983 (Box 275, Folder 10)
  - Annual Survey, 1984 (Box 275, Folder 11)
  - Annual Survey, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 12)
  - Annual Survey, 1986 (Box 275, Folder 13)
  - Annual Survey, 1987 (Box 275, Folder 14)
  - Annual Survey, 1988 (Box 275, Folder 15)
  - Annual Survey, 1989 (Box 275, Folder 16)
  - Annual Survey, 1990 (Box 275, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, Annual Survey, 1991 (Box 275, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, Annual Survey, 1992 (Box 275, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, Annual Survey, 1993 (Box 275, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, Annual Survey, 1994 (Box 275, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, Annual Survey, Annual Highlights, 1995 (Box 275, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, Annual Survey, Annual Highlights, 1996 (Box 275, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 275, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 275, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 275, Folder 26)
  - Annual Reports, 2000-2010 (Box 275, Folder 27)
  - General and Miscellaneous Publications (Box 276-294)
    In process, please direct any question to archives@mail.lib.cua.edu.
- Series 10: Awards, n.d.; (1 Box)
  Box 295. This small series in process, we hope to have box contents posted soon. In the meantime, please direct any question to archives@mail.lib.cua.edu.